clicker.com 2011-05-15

# Privacy Policy - Clicker.com

**Effective: December 15, 2010**

Welcome to the Clicker Media Inc. ("Clicker") web site and online services (the "Site"). Clicker values the privacy of our members and others who visit and use the Site (individually, “you” or collectively, “Users”). We take your privacy seriously and make it a priority to protect personally identifiable information that we obtain from and about individuals both online and off-line. 

This Privacy Policy describes what information we gather from you, how we use that information, and what we do to protect it. By using the Site (whether or not you are a registered member), you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this policy. If you do not want information about you to be used in the manner set forth in this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Clicker Terms of Service. Your use of the Site and any personal information you provide on the Site are subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and Clicker's Terms of Service. 

### The Information Clicker Collects

_User-provided Information:_ When you register as a member of the Site, you may provide to Clicker what is generally called "personally identifiable" information (such as your name, password, gender, email address, postal mailing address, home/mobile telephone number), short biography, a picture. From time to time, Clicker may also ask you optionally to provide other information. If you choose to provide such information, you are giving Clicker the permission to use and store it consistent with this policy. Therefore, please understand that when you sign in with Clicker, you are not anonymous to us. 

_Social Information:_ Our Site is designed to allow you to make connections with other users, communicate with them about your tastes, and help you share that information with the community and to the world. This includes your check-ins, comments and ratings about content on the Site, when you checked-in, commented or rated content, and the metadata around those check-ins, ratings or content. It also includes the playlists you create, the people you follow, the content you mark as favorites and many other pieces of information. Our default is almost always to make the information you provide public but we provide you settings to make the information private if you prefer. This public information can be broadly and instantly disseminated. For example, your public comments and ratings are searchable by many search engines and can be immediately delivered via our Application Programming Interfaces ("API"s) to a wide range of users and services. 

The Site also allows you to connect with certain third party services (e.g., Twitter, Facebook and other similar services). When you broadcast information to such third party services, such information is no longer under the control of Clicker and is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of such third parties. In order to enhance and personalize your use of Clicker, some of those third party services may also provide Clicker with information from your accounts there. For example, you can allow Facebook to tell us who your Facebook friends are so you can follow their activity on Clicker as well as what your Facebook Likes are so that we can provide you with personalized recommendations. You can adjust your Clicker account settings to block this feature, in which case we will delete the information that we receive from your accounts with those other services. To read more about the Facebook Instant Personalization partnership, click here. You can also further modify your privacy settings with those third party services directly. For example, you can adjust your privacy setting on Facebook [here](http://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=privacy) to opt out of the Facebook Instant Personalization and prevent your Facebook friends from sharing information about you from their Facebook accounts with Clicker. Additionally, certain information may be made available to third party developers using our API. Use of third party services developed using our API are subject to the terms of use and privacy policies of such third party developers. 

_"Cookies" Information:_ When you visit the Site, whether or not you are a registered member, we may send one or more cookies - small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters-to your computer. Cookies remember information about your activities on a website. Clicker may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed. Please review your web browser "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. However, without cookies you will not have access to certain services on the Site. Third party advertisements displayed in connection with the Site may also contain cookies set by internet advertisers. We do not control these cookies and users of the Site should check the privacy policy of the advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. 

### The Way Clicker Uses Information

Clicker collects personally identifiable information when you register as a member in order to establish and enhance our relationship with you. Clicker generally uses the information you provide or that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features and services found on the Site. We will also display a portion of your personal information in your profile page and elsewhere on the Site (for example, when you post a comment) according to the preferences you set in your member account. You can review and revise your profile information at any time, as explained below (see “ **Your Choices** ”). If you have given Clicker consent, we may use your personally identifiable information to provide you with information about Clicker's features, services and other offerings that may be of interest to you. We may also send information or offers to groups of users on behalf of other businesses. Under certain circumstances (for example if you win a contest) we may post your personally identifiable information on the Site. However, we will notify you of this possibility when collecting personally identifiable information or we will obtain your consent. We may share your personally identifiable information with certain other websites that we link to (and that you click upon) in order to enhance your experience in connection with the Site. 

Clicker uses all of the information that we collect from Users to understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of our Users, to improve the way the Site works and looks, and to create new features and functionality. 

Clicker may use "cookies" information to: (a) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Site; (b) provide customized third-party advertisements, content, and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of third-party marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities. If you have registered as a member and given Clicker consent, we may share your personally identifiable information with advertisers, business partners, and other entities that are not affiliated with Clicker who would like to send you information about their products and services. Clicker's employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to the personally identifiable information you may provide to register as a member of Clicker. We may share your personally identifiable information with companies that provide services to us, including outside contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities (for example, contest and sweepstakes administration), but they may only use your personally identifiable information to provide us with a specific service and not for any other purpose. 

### Anonymous Aggregated Data

Anonymous data is information (originally personally identifiable or non-personally identifiable) that subsequently is used in aggregate form. We may collect anonymous data whether or not you are a registered member of the Site. We may use anonymous data for purposes of research or analysis. We may conduct research on our customer demographics, internet usage, and interests and behavior based on personal data we gather. Although anonymous data may be based in part on personal data, it does not identify you personally. 

Clicker may share this type of anonymous data with a variety of third parties, including its affiliates, advertisers and other current and prospective business partners. Clicker may use anonymous data collected for website administration, advertising and promotional purposes, and we may share such information with various affiliated and unaffiliated entities for such purposes. We may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess technology that allows us to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive while using the Site. Your non-personally identifiable information and click stream data about your activities may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished. Our agreement with these companies prohibits them from sharing your information with any third party or using it for any other purpose. Anonymous click stream and demographic information may also be shared with our advertisers and business partners. 

### When Clicker Discloses Information

Clicker discloses automatically collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information with interested third parties to assist such parties in understanding the usage, viewing, and demographic patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Site. 

Clicker may also disclose User information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant. In some cases, we may make such disclosures without first providing notice to Users. 

Clicker also reserves the right to disclose User information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; protect Clicker from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Site; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Clicker, our Users, or others. 

### Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to share your personally-identifiable information with Clicker, in which case Clicker will not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality found on the Site. If you register as a member of Clicker, you may update, correct, or delete your profile information and preferences at any time by emailing us at _[privacy@clicker.com](mailto:privacy@clicker.com)_. 

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you account access or making corrections to your information. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

### Third-Party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites

The Site may be linked to internet websites operated by other companies. Some of these websites may be co-branded with our name or logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by us. Clicker may also permit other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks may use technology to send, directly to your browser, some of the advertisements and links that appear on the Site. These advertisers may automatically receive your IP address if this happens. These advertisers may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party websites and third party ad servers or ad networks. Clicker's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other third party advertisers or web sites. Please be aware that Clicker does not warn you when you have chosen to link through to another website from the Site. 

### Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Clicker does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on the Site from persons under 13 years-of-age. If Clicker learns that personally-identifiable information of persons less than 13-years-of-age has been collected on Clicker without verifiable parental consent, then Clicker will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child under the age of 13 has obtained a Site account, then you may alert Clicker at _[privacy@clicker.com](mailto:privacy@clicker.com)_ and request that Clicker delete that child's personal information from its systems. 

### Our Commitment to Data Security

Clicker uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Clicker, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Clicker makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If Clicker learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Clicker may post a notice on the Site if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. 

### International Visitors

The Site is hosted in the United States and is intended solely for visitors located within the United States. If you nonetheless choose to use the Site from the European Union or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, then please note that you are transferring your personally identifiable information outside of those regions to the United States and by providing your personally identifiable information on the Site you consent to that transfer. 

### In the Event of Merger or Sale

In the event that Clicker is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. 

### Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy

Clicker reserves the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. If we modify this Privacy Policy, we will post the modification on the Site. We will also indicate when such revised Privacy Policy is effective at the top of the page. Your continued use of the Site after the posting of changes constitutes your binding acceptance of such changes. If the modified Privacy Policy is not acceptable to you, your only recourse is to cease using the Site. 

### Clicker Contact Information

Please contact Clicker with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, our third-party disclosure practices, or your consent choices by email at _[privacy@clicker.com](mailto:privacy@clicker.com)_ or by mail at: 

**Attention: Privacy Officer  
Clicker Media Inc.  
6824 Melrose Ave.  
Los Angeles, CA 90038 **
